# Sebastian Gołąb

Phone:

+48 886 165 556

Email:

sebagolab97@gmail .com

Date of birth:

02-08-1997

City:

Wadowice

### **ABOUT ME**

I works as a programmer since 2017, I specialize in as frontend developer who makes new projects and advances existing ones. I am independent but also I good feel in team work where together we can develop our competencies.

I am person who not only creates code, but also engages in the full scope of the design process. I will be happy to share my experience and knowledge to create unique solutions together.

### **EXPERIENCE**

1. Web Developer, Intermania Wadowice - from 2017 to 10 may 2022

In Intermania i made many projects in Wordpress, every website was maked on template which i design in figma and wrote from zero. I participated in every website process from talking with clients to final product.

2. Frontend Developer, Home.pl S.A. - from 10 may 2022 to now

At Home.pl I work as frontend developer in team who work on one large ecommerce project, we make new solutions, develop our project in terms of performance and fix bugs. I cooperate with UX and UI designers and business teams to make best product for our clients.

### **EDUCATION**

CKZiU number 2 in Wadowice, IT profile — from 2013 to 2017

## **PORTFOLIO**

https://sebastiangolab.pl/

## **SKILLS - TOOLS AND TECHNOLOGIES**

HTML5, CSS3, Javascript ES6+, TypeScript, React, React Native, Gatsby, Next.js, Redux, REST API, Webpack, Styled Components, Sass, Bootstrap, Headless CMS, GraphQL, Wordpress, Prestashop, Jest, GIT, GSAP, MySQL, Figma, Spline

## **ADDITIONAL SKILLS**

Working in Scrum, SEO, AdWords, WCAG, designing website templates in figma, ability to manage social media channels, working with databases,

hosting support, ability to work in a team, experience in creating new projects from scratch

## **LANGUAGES**

Polish, English (B1)

I consent to the processing of my personal data for the purpose of recruiting for the position I am applying for.